I have some good news to share.
لدي بعض الأخبار السارة لأشاركها معكم.
Xiaoxiao is awake.
Xiaoxiao مستيقظ.
Once he can speak,
بمجرد أن يتمكن من الكلام،
everyone will know the truth.
سيعرف الجميع الحقيقة.
Dafo's child is awake.
طفل دافو مستيقظ.
Didn't they say he needed several dialysis sessions?
ألم يقولوا إنه يحتاج إلى عدة جلسات غسيل كلى؟
Xiao Bai.
شياو باي.
Do you dare to go to the hospital with me to confront this?
هل تجرؤ على الذهاب معي إلى المستشفى لمواجهة هذا الأمر؟
This rundown hospital in Old Street
هذا المستشفى المتهالك في شارع أولد ستريت
couldn't cure such severe poisoning so quickly.
لم يكن بالإمكان علاج مثل هذا التسمم الشديد بهذه السرعة.
This kid is trying to bluff me.
هذا الطفل يحاول خداعي.
Fine, let's go.
حسناً، لنذهب.
I have a clear conscience.
ضميري مرتاح.
Right, right, right.
صحيح، صحيح، صحيح.
Doctor!
طبيب!
How's my child?
كيف حال طفلي؟
Don't worry, family.
لا تقلقوا يا أهلي.
He's been cured.
لقد شُفي.
He'll be wheeled out shortly.
سيتم إخراجه قريباً.
Okay, okay.
حسناً، حسناً.
My Xiaoxiao.
بلدي شياوشياو.
Doctor!
طبيب!
Please help him quickly.
أرجوكم ساعدوه بسرعة.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Come in.
ادخل.
Go ahead first.
تفضل أولاً.
Xiao Bai.
شياو باي.
Weren't we going to confront each other?
ألم نكن سنواجه بعضنا البعض؟
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Go.
يذهب.
That's great.
هذا رائع.
My Xiaoxiao.
بلدي شياوشياو.
He's finally better.
لقد تحسنت حالته أخيراً.
Zhao Fengsheng.
تشاو فنغ شنغ.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
I heard Xiaoxiao was waking up.
سمعت أن شياو شياو كانت تستيقظ.
I'm here to prove my innocence, of course.
أنا هنا لأثبت براءتي، بالطبع.
I won't let you see my Xiaoxiao.
لن أدعك ترى شياو شياو خاصتي.
Auntie Feng.
العمة فنغ.
So many people are watching.
يشاهد الكثير من الناس.
What else are you worried about?
ما الذي يقلقك أيضاً؟
Besides,
بجانب،
I was the one who changed Xiaoxiao's attending doctor.
أنا من قام بتغيير الطبيب المعالج لشياو شياو.
You...
أنت...
Otherwise, how could he have woken up so early?
وإلا، كيف كان بإمكانه أن يستيقظ مبكراً جداً؟
You're a loser who can't even afford pickled vegetables.
أنت شخص فاشل لا تستطيع حتى شراء الخضراوات المخللة.
How could you afford to hire a specialist?
كيف استطعت تحمل تكلفة توظيف متخصص؟
I did see a new doctor arrive earlier.
لقد رأيت طبيباً جديداً يصل في وقت سابق.
It was you, Yuchen, who invited him, right?
أنت يا يوتشن من دعاه، أليس كذلك؟
Xiaoxiao, Xiaoxiao.
شياو شياو، شياو شياو.
Xiaoxiao.
شياوشياو.
My good grandson.
حفيدي العزيز.
Daddy.
بابي.
Grandpa.
جدي.
Grandma.
جدتي.
Grandma missed you so much.
جدتي اشتاقت إليك كثيراً.
Good boy, my good boy.
يا ولدي الطيب، يا ولدي الطيب.
Little chick.
كتكوت صغير.
Chicken Uncle.
عم الدجاج.
You little rascal, you do remember me.
أيها الوغد الصغير، أنت تتذكرني.
Chicken Uncle, hold me.
يا عم الدجاج، أمسك بي.
What are you trying to do?
ماذا تحاول أن تفعل؟
Still trying to lay a hand on our Xiaoxiao?
هل ما زلت تحاول أن تضع يدك على شياو شياو خاصتنا؟
You blockhead.
يا غبي.
Your son just asked for a hug.
طلب ابنك للتو عناقاً.
Why don't you get it?
لماذا لا تفهم ذلك؟
Xiaoxiao.
شياوشياو.
Do you remember the bad guy who tied you up that day?
هل تتذكر الرجل الشرير الذي قام بتقييدك في ذلك اليوم؟
I don't remember.
أنا لا أتذكر.
See?
يرى؟
I told you so.
قلت لك ذلك.
Zhao Fengsheng is a liar.
تشاو فنغ شنغ كاذب.
I only remember an uncle who saved me.
لا أتذكر سوى عمي الذي أنقذني.
He told me not to sleep.
قال لي ألا أنام.
Otherwise, if I slept too much, I wouldn't see Daddy
وإلا، إذا نمت كثيراً، فلن أرى أبي
or Grandpa and Grandma.
أو الجد والجدة.
My good boy.
يا ولدي الطيب.
You've suffered so much.
لقد عانيت كثيراً.
Xiaoxiao.
شياوشياو.
Tell Daddy,
قل لأبيك،
exactly which uncle saved you?
أي عم أنقذك تحديداً؟
Him?
له؟
Which one?
أيها؟
Him.
له.
Xiaoxiao.
شياوشياو.
It was me.
كنت أنا.
I was the one who carried you back that day.
أنا من حملتكِ عائدةً في ذلك اليوم.
Have you forgotten?
هل نسيت؟
Hug.
حضن.
Chicken Uncle.
عم الدجاج.
The one who saved me was Chicken Uncle.
الشخص الذي أنقذني هو العم تشيكن.
Really?
حقًا؟
I wouldn't remember wrong.
لن أخطئ في التذكر.
Good child.
طفل صالح.
So good.
جيد جداً.
It really was him.
كان هو بالفعل.
Now the truth is clear, right?
الآن باتت الحقيقة واضحة، أليس كذلك؟
Could it be...
هل يمكن أن يكون...
that it really was Shengzi who saved Xiaoxiao?
هل كان شينغزي هو من أنقذ شياو شياو حقًا؟
Manager Bai
المدير باي
Dafo
كدح
Uh...
أوه...
The child just woke up.
استيقظ الطفل للتو.
He's not fully conscious yet.
لم يعد واعياً تماماً بعد.
Now that things have come to this,
والآن وقد وصلت الأمور إلى هذا الحد،
Manager Bai, tell us the truth.
يا مدير باي، قل لنا الحقيقة.
What exactly is your connection
ما هي صلتك تحديداً؟
to those traffickers from Daixiang Village?
إلى هؤلاء المتاجرين بالبشر من قرية دايكسيانغ؟
Bai Yuchen!
باي يوشين!
Did you poison our Xiaoxiao?
هل سممت شياو شياو خاصتنا؟
Talk!
يتحدث!
It's a misunderstanding!
إنه سوء فهم!
A misunderstanding!
سوء فهم!
Here's what happened.
إليكم ما حدث.
Xiaoxiao was already unconscious.
كانت شياو شياو قد فقدت وعيها بالفعل.
I was afraid of delaying his treatment,
كنت أخشى تأخير علاجه،
so I helped you get the child back.
لذلك ساعدتك في استعادة الطفل.
Really!
حقًا!
You really have some nerve!
لديك جرأة كبيرة حقاً!
I risked my life to save Xiaoxiao.
لقد خاطرت بحياتي لإنقاذ شياو شياو.
I told you to bring the child back first.
قلت لك أن تعيد الطفل أولاً.
But what did you do?
لكن ماذا فعلت؟
You pinned the trafficker label on me!
لقد ألصقت بي تهمة الاتجار بالبشر!
And you made it sound so noble!
وجعلتَ الأمر يبدو نبيلاً للغاية!
Even though
بالرغم من
you, Zhao Fengsheng, carried the child back,
أنت يا تشاو فنغشنغ، حملت الطفل عائدًا،
but
لكن
who's to say
من يستطيع الجزم؟
you weren't just putting on an act
لم تكن مجرد تمثيلية
to avoid being blamed by the neighbors?
لتجنب إلقاء اللوم على الجيران؟
You were faking it!
كنتَ تتظاهر!
At a time like this,
في مثل هذا الوقت،
you still want to call me a trafficker?
هل ما زلت تريد أن تصفني بالمتاجر بالبشر؟
Yes!
نعم!
You ARE a trafficker, you hear me?
أنت تاجر مخدرات، هل تسمعني؟
Bai Yuchen,
باي يوشين,
you've been deceiving us for so long.
لقد كنت تخدعنا لفترة طويلة.
From now on, you're banned from Old Street.
من الآن فصاعدًا، أنت ممنوع من دخول شارع أولد ستريت.
And another thing!
وأمر آخر!
Don't you dare try to ruin
إياك أن تحاول التدمير
Shengzi and Er Ni's relationship!
علاقة شينغزي وإر ني!
Do you understand?
هل تفهم؟
Exactly!
بالضبط!
You Bai family scoundrel!
يا وغد عائلة باي!
So you're that kind of a swindler!
إذن أنت من هذا النوع من المحتالين!
You schemed and caused all this trouble
لقد تآمرت وتسببت في كل هذه المشاكل
just to trick our Er Ni into marriage, right?
فقط لخداع إر ني وإجبارها على الزواج، أليس كذلك؟
Thank goodness
شكرا لله
we saw your true colors today.
لقد رأينا حقيقتك اليوم.
Mother-in-law...
حماة " أم الزوج أو أم الزوجة...
Now that's not fair to say.
هذا ليس من العدل أن نقول ذلك.
Wasn't it you
ألم تكن أنت؟
who coveted my position as Qian Group manager
الذين كانوا يطمعون في منصبي كمدير لمجموعة تشيان
and pushed your daughter onto me?
ودفعت ابنتك نحوي؟
You!
أنت!
And you, "Buddha"!
وأنت يا "بوذا"!
I'm talking to you!
أنا أتحدث إليك!
Aren't you afraid I'll make
ألا تخشى أن أجعلك
all of you starve?
هل ستجوعون جميعاً؟
Who do you think you're talking to?
من تظن أنك تتحدث إليه؟
So arrogant!
يا له من غرور!
Seems to me
يبدو لي
you're the one who'll be starving.
أنت من سيتضور جوعاً.
Let me tell you,
دعني أخبرك،
I
أنا
am a manager of the Qian Group!
أنا مدير في مجموعة تشيان!
Crushing you
سحقك
is as easy as squashing bugs!
الأمر سهل كسحق الحشرات!
Is your power really that great?
هل قوتك عظيمة إلى هذا الحد؟
Anyone who didn't know better
أي شخص لم يكن يعرف أفضل
would think you're the chairman of the Qian Group.
قد يظن المرء أنك رئيس مجلس إدارة مجموعة تشيان.
Ch-Chairman Qian!
الرئيس تشيان!
Y-you...
أنتَ...
What brings you here?
ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا؟
You should have told me,
كان ينبغي عليك إخباري،
given me a call.
اتصل بي.
Bai Yuchen,
باي يوشين,
I hereby officially notify you
أُبلغكم رسمياً بموجب هذا
that you are fired from the Qian Group.
أنك مطرود من مجموعة تشيان.
Furthermore, in Bianshui,
علاوة على ذلك، في بيانشوي،
any industry related to the Qian Group
أي صناعة ذات صلة بمجموعة تشيان
will blacklist you.
سيتم إدراجك في القائمة السوداء.
Serves you right! See if you dare strut now.
تستحق ذلك! انظر إن كنت تجرؤ على التبختر الآن.
No, no, no!
لا، لا، لا!
Please!
لو سمحت!
Chairman Qian, please don't!
الرئيس تشيان، أرجوك لا تفعل!
My heart was only for
كان قلبي مخصصًا فقط لـ
the development of our Qian Group!
تطوير مجموعة تشيان الخاصة بنا!
Y-you must give me another chance!
يجب أن تمنحني فرصة أخرى!
You offended Mr. Zhao,
لقد أسأت إلى السيد تشاو،
and you still dare to babble here?
وما زلت تجرؤ على الثرثرة هنا؟
Throw him out.
أخرجوه من هنا.
No, wait!
لا، انتظر!
Mr. Zhao is...
السيد تشاو هو...
Mr. Zhao!
السيد تشاو!
I've offended you.
لقد أسأت إليك.
No.
لا.
Zhao... Zhao Fengsheng.
تشاو ... تشاو فنغ شنغ.
No, no.
لا لا.
Shengzi, Shengzi.
شينغزي، شينغزي.
Please help me.
أرجوكم ساعدوني.
I can't lose my job.
لا يمكنني أن أفقد وظيفتي.
Before, on Old Street...
في السابق، في شارع أولد ستريت...
Er Ni, it was all my fault.
يا إلهي، كان كل ذلك خطأي.
I'm a jerk.
أنا شخص سيء.
You can't make me lose my job.
لا يمكنك أن تجعلني أفقد وظيفتي.
Get out.
اخرج.
Please help me.
أرجوكم ساعدوني.
I'm a jerk, Shengzi.
أنا أحمق، Shengzi.
Get out!
اخرج!
I can't be without a job.
لا أستطيع البقاء بدون وظيفة.
I have an old mother to support.
لدي أم مسنة أعيلها.
Shengzi, I'm begging you.
شينغزي، أتوسل إليك.
Zhao Fengsheng.
تشاو فنغ شنغ.
Brother Zhao.
الأخ تشاو.
I'm truly sorry.
أنا آسف حقاً.
That the Qian Group has such scum.
أن تضم مجموعة تشيان مثل هؤلاء الحثالة.
Caused you trouble.
لقد سببت لك مشاكل.
It's fine.
لا بأس.
Chairman Qian, you've helped a lot already.
الرئيس تشيان، لقد قدمت الكثير من المساعدة بالفعل.
Neighbors.
الجيران.
This is the chairman of the Qian Group.
هذا هو رئيس مجلس إدارة مجموعة تشيان.
Chairman Qian.
الرئيس تشيان.
The one who changed Xiaoxiao's doctor.
الشخص الذي غيّر طبيب شياو شياو.
Is him.
هو هو.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Thank you, Chairman Qian.
شكراً لك، الرئيس تشيان.
Ma'am.
سيدتي.
You're welcome.
على الرحب والسعة.
This is all because of Brother Shengzi.
كل هذا بفضل الأخ شينغزي.
That we stepped in to help.
لقد تدخلنا للمساعدة.
Shengzi.
شينغزي.
Before, Auntie wrongly blamed you.
في السابق، ألقت العمة اللوم عليك ظلماً.
Auntie shouldn't have listened to that Manager Bai.
كان ينبغي على العمة ألا تستمع إلى ذلك المدير باي.
That liar's nonsense.
هذا هراء كاذب.
Auntie thanks you for saving our Xiaoxiao.
تشكرك عمتي على إنقاذ شياو شياو خاصتنا.
Auntie is...
العمة هي...
Apologizing to you.
أعتذر لك.
Someone your age kneeling to me...
شخص في مثل سنك يركع أمامي...
Will shorten my life!
سيقصر ذلك حياتي!
I should be kneeling to you.
كان ينبغي أن أكون راكعاً أمامك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
We're all neighbors here.
كلنا جيران هنا.
As long as the misunderstanding is cleared up.
طالما تم توضيح سوء الفهم.
Shengzi.
شينغزي.
Shengzi is magnanimous.
شينغزي شخص كريم.
This old man is also embarrassed.
هذا الرجل العجوز يشعر بالحرج أيضاً.
Oh, come on.
هيا بنا.
What are you saying.
ماذا تقول.
I'm all...
أنا كل...
Embarrassed now.
أشعر بالحرج الآن.
But I've left you some time.
لكنني تركت لك بعض الوقت.
I want to hear how you'll praise me.
أريد أن أسمع كيف ستثني عليّ.
For... for a whole day?
لمدة... ليوم كامل؟
Yeah.
نعم.
I suffered such great injustice.
لقد تعرضت لظلم كبير.
Shouldn't you praise me properly?
ألا ينبغي عليك أن تثني عليّ كما ينبغي؟
But no repeating.
لكن لا تكرار.
Alright, alright.
حسناً، حسناً.
Okay, okay, okay.
حسناً، حسناً، حسناً.
Okay.
تمام.
You chased me away the hardest.
لقد طردتني بشدة.
Dafo.
تحليل SWOT.
Then... then...
ثم... ثم...
Then I'll praise you for two days.
ثم سأمدحك لمدة يومين.
Two days.
يومين.
Auntie.
خالتي.
You hit me the hardest.
لقد أثرت بي بشدة.
Misunderstanding.
سوء الفهم.
It was all a misunderstanding.
كان الأمر كله سوء فهم.
Misunderstanding, misunderstanding, misunderstanding.
سوء فهم، سوء فهم، سوء فهم.
Misunderstanding, misunderstanding.
سوء فهم، سوء فهم.
As long as it's a misunderstanding.
طالما أنه مجرد سوء فهم.
Xiaoxiao.
شياوشياو.
Do you know why Chicken Uncle...
هل تعرف لماذا عم الدجاج...
Is called Chicken Uncle?
هل يُطلق عليه اسم "عم الدجاج"؟
You loved eating chicken since you were little.
كنت تحب أكل الدجاج منذ صغرك.
You ate all the chickens in my house.
أكلت كل الدجاج في منزلي.
Right, right, right.
صحيح، صحيح، صحيح.
Exactly, exactly.
بالضبط، بالضبط.
It's because...
ذلك لأن...
I grew up eating from a hundred homes.
نشأت وأنا أتناول الطعام من مئة منزل.
Right.
يمين.
From now on, the chickens in our house...
من الآن فصاعدًا، الدجاج في منزلنا...
Will be ready for you too.
سأكون جاهزاً لك أيضاً.
Always ready for you.
جاهزون دائماً من أجلك.
Right.
يمين.
Shengzi.
شينغزي.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
From now on, our Old Street...
من الآن فصاعدًا، شارعنا القديم...
Will always be your family.
سنبقى عائلتكم دائماً.
Family.
عائلة.
Family, family.
العائلة، العائلة.
What?
ماذا؟
You want me to apologize to that jerk Zhao Fengsheng?
أتريدني أن أعتذر لذلك الأحمق تشاو فنغشنغ؟
Dad.
أب.
You might not know this,
ربما لا تعلم هذا،
Ya Qing almost had a marriage ruined because of him.
كادت يا تشينغ أن تفقد زواجها بسببه.
And she was seriously injured.
وأصيبت بجروح خطيرة.
How can I apologize to such scum?
كيف لي أن أعتذر لمثل هؤلاء الأوغاد؟
Wouldn't that make our Qian family lose face?
ألن يؤدي ذلك إلى فقدان عائلة تشيان لمكانتها؟
Take that Bai Yuchen under you,
خذ ذلك باي يوتشن تحتك،
he's a typical selfish person.
إنه شخص أناني نموذجي.
He even dared to steal credit from Mr. Zhao.
بل إنه تجرأ على سرقة الفضل من السيد تشاو.
I've already kicked him out of the group.
لقد طردته بالفعل من المجموعة.
What?
ماذا؟
How could Manager Bai be such a person?
كيف يمكن أن يكون المدير باي شخصًا كهذا؟
Dad, are you mistaken?
أبي، هل أنت مخطئ؟
He usually acts...
هو عادة ما يتصرف...
Tianyu.
تيانيو.
You will have to manage the group someday.
سيتعين عليك إدارة المجموعة يوماً ما.
You must learn to judge people.
يجب أن تتعلم كيف تحكم على الناس.
Just now at the hospital,
الآن في المستشفى،
the child named Xiaoxiao,
الطفل المسمى شياو شياو،
in front of everyone,
أمام الجميع،
has already confirmed it.
وقد أكد ذلك بالفعل.
How could this be?
كيف يمكن أن يكون هذا؟
I almost married Ya Qing to him.
كدتُ أزوج يا تشينغ له.
What have I done?
ماذا فعلت؟
But, Dad,
لكن يا أبي،
that Zhao Fengsheng,
أن تشاو فنغ شنغ،
he's definitely not a good person.
إنه بالتأكيد ليس شخصاً جيداً.
He's just a petty person trying to use our Qian family
إنه مجرد شخص تافه يحاول استغلال عائلة تشيان الخاصة بنا
to climb the social ladder.
للارتقاء في السلم الاجتماعي.
He usually...
هو عادة...
I don't care how much you dislike him now.
لا يهمني مدى كرهك له الآن.
In the face of the entire Qian family's future,
في مواجهة مستقبل عائلة تشيان بأكملها،
it's not worth mentioning.
لا يستحق الأمر الذكر.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
The Tang family
عائلة تانغ
is already about to move against our Qian family.
هو على وشك التحرك ضد عائلة تشيان.
For our Qian family to survive,
لكي تبقى عائلة تشيان على قيد الحياة،
we must have Zhao Fengsheng
يجب أن يكون لدينا تشاو فنغ شنغ
ask Li Xiangping for help and support.
اطلب المساعدة والدعم من لي شيانغ بينغ.
Only then do we have a slim chance.
عندها فقط ستكون لدينا فرصة ضئيلة.
Young Master Li?
السيد الشاب لي؟
How could Zhao Fengsheng possibly know Young Master Li?
كيف يمكن أن يكون تشاو فنغشنغ قد عرف السيد الشاب لي؟
Dad, you must be mistaken.
يا أبي، لا بد أنك مخطئ.
Zhao Fengsheng
تشاو فنغ شنغ
is the guest that Young Master Li
هو الضيف الذي استضافته السيدة الشابة لي
personally called to ask me to look after,
اتصل بي شخصياً ليطلب مني أن أعتني بـ
the one I waited all day to receive.
الذي انتظرته طوال اليوم لأستلمه.